We can't
be friends if you insult me, and I don't give a damn
whether it's a joke or not
.  No, I don't need that, because it's
not fun for me if you jokingly
tell me I'm ugly.  The
[ __ ].  We can't be friends
if you're a boy-crazy guy.  I hate
girls like that so much.  As soon as male
creatures, male beings
are near him, he has a completely different
personality, a completely different
voice, which is ten levels higher.
I really don't feel like doing that.  Please stay away
from me.  We can't
be friends if you're disrespectful
.  Whether it's with any waiters,
any salespeople, or my
family, I find that kind of thing so uncomfortable.
My second-hand embarrassment is up there.